http://www.shoestoboot.com/privacy-policy.html

Davidson Shoes
Exceptional customer service since 1894!
Menu
Home
WomensWomen's ShoesWomen's BootsWomen's SandalsWomen's ClogsWomen's SlippersWomen's Insoles & OrthoticsWomen's SocksMensMen's BootsMen's ShoesMen's SandalsMen's ClogsMen's SlippersMen's Insoles & OrthoticsMen's SocksKidsKid's SandalsKid's ShoesKid's BootsKid's SlippersBrandsAcorn Slippers & ShoesArcopedico ShoesAsolo Hiking & Backpacking BootsBirkenstock Sandals, Shoes & ClogsBlackstone BootsBlundstone Boots & ShoesBOGS BootsCarolina Work & Uniform BootsChaco SandalsChippewa BootsClarks Shoes & BootsColumbia BootsDansko FootwearEarth Shoes, Boots & SandalsEcco Sandals & ShoesHaflinger Clogs, Shoes & SlippersHoka One One ShoesKeen Sandals, Shoes & BootsKlogs ShoesLa Sportiva Boots & ShoesLowa BootsMerrell Sandals, Shoes & BootsMinnetonka MoccasinsNaot Shoes, Sandals, Clogs & BootsNew Balance ShoesOlukai Saldals & ShoesPapillio SandalsPendleton BootsReebok Shoes & BootsRemonte Shoes & SandalsRieker Shoes & BootsSperry Shoes & BootsTaos Shoes, Clogs, Sandals & BootsTeva Sandals & ShoesUGG Australia Boots, Shoes & SlippersVasque Boots & ShoesWolky Clogs, Shoes & SandalsGSAAbout UsContact Us
Home
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Davidson Shoes Plus is committed to safeguarding your privacy online. We do not
give or sell your personally identifiable information to anyone except under special
circumstances, such as when we believe in good faith that the law requires it.
As with all personal information, Davidson Shoes will never rent or
sell your personal financial information. We may occasionally use the e-mail or
residential address that you supply to send you information regarding sales, product
updates, specials, etc. pertaining to this web site. Upon your request, you will be removed from our mailing list.
Security
Keeping your personal information secure and private is vitally important
to us. In order to prevent unauthorised access or
disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and
secure the information we collect online.
How we use cookies
A cookie is a small file which stores information about your website visits. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The website can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about
your preferences.
Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website experience.
A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you,
other than the data you choose to share with us. You can choose to accept or decline cookies.
Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting
to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of our website.
List of cookies we collect
The table below lists the cookies we collect and what information they store.
Cookie Name
Cookie Description
FORM_KEY
Stores randomly generated key used to prevent forged requests.
PHPSESSID
Your session ID on the server.
GUEST-VIEW
Allows guests to view and edit their orders.
PERSISTENT_SHOPPING_CART
A link to information about your cart and viewing history, if you have asked for this.
STF
Information on products you have emailed to friends.
STORE
The store view or language you have selected.
USER_ALLOWED_SAVE_COOKIE
Indicates whether a customer allowed to use cookies.
MAGE-CACHE-SESSID
Facilitates caching of content on the browser to make pages load faster.
MAGE-CACHE-STORAGE
Facilitates caching of content on the browser to make pages load faster.
MAGE-CACHE-STORAGE-SECTION-INVALIDATION
Facilitates caching of content on the browser to make pages load faster.
MAGE-CACHE-TIMEOUT
Facilitates caching of content on the browser to make pages load faster.
SECTION-DATA-IDS
Facilitates caching of content on the browser to make pages load faster.
PRIVATE_CONTENT_VERSION
Facilitates caching of content on the browser to make pages load faster.
X-MAGENTO-VARY
Facilitates caching of content on the server to make pages load faster.
MAGE-TRANSLATION-FILE-VERSION
Facilitates translation of content to other languages.
MAGE-TRANSLATION-STORAGE
Facilitates translation of content to other languages.
